

## Contact

#### **Email**

kverenchkhiladzeirakli.personal@gmail.com

**Address** 

Tbilisi, Georgia

Portfolio

Link

## **Skills**

**Javascript** 

**Typescript** 

React.js

Vue.js

Three.js

Next.js

Nuxt.js

Node.js

Express.js

Svelte

React Three Fiber

Redux

**Tailwindcss** 

Jest

Cypress

VITE

HTML/CSS/SCSS

And much more ...

## Language

English B2/C1

Russian A2/B1

# Irakli Kvernechkiladze

## Software Developer

Experienced software developer with 5 years of experience. Skilled in programming, web development, e-commerce, back-end, VR, AR, and video games. Developed core data visualization applications used in **CERN's** largest experiment and presented them at ICHEP2020.

Primary Technologies: Typescript, React, Next.js, Three.js, Redux, Express.js, TailwindCSS

## **Experience**

O 2018 - Current

**CERN** 

### **Fullstack Developer**

Developed high-level visualization 12 different applications for scientific communities, research groups, and students. Participated in workshops, Demonstrated applications to different groups and teams at **CERN** 

#### Responsibilities:

- Upgraded 3 applications with technologies such as React TailwindCss Three.js Redux.
- Created "CORE" library for 12 different applications
- Analyzed and profiled of application performance to identify areas of improvement.
- Optimized loading strategy for models, reducing size, and enhancing app loading speed.
- Participated in code reviews and ensured code quality and best practices.

#### 2023 - Current

Sohohouse

#### Frontend Developer

Soho House is a global hotel chain and group of private members' clubs originally aimed at those in the arts and media.

#### Responsibilities:

- Developed and maintained web application using Vue.js and Nuxt.js.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams.
- Participated in code reviews.
- Wrote and maintaining technical documentation.
- Identified and addressing performance issues.

### 2022 - 2023

Basic-Fit

### **Backend Developer**

With over millions of members and more than 1100 clubs, Basic-Fit is the European leader in the low-cost fitness market and the fastest growing fitness brand in Europe.

#### Responsibilities :

- Developed, maintained, and troubleshoot server side code in SFCC(SalesForce).
- Designed and implemented RESTful APIs.
- Implemented and customized SFCC features such as promotions, checkout flows, etc..
- Collaborated with front-end developers to deliver seamless user experiences.

## **Addition**

#### **Education**

Currently studying Computer Science in Georgian Technical University

### **Participation**

Teaching students Front-End Developement



## Contact

#### **Email**

kverenchkhiladzeirakli.personal@gmail.com

**Address** 

Tbilisi, Georgia

**Portfolio** 

<u>Link</u>

## **Skills**

Javascript

**Typescript** 

React.js

Vue.js

Three.js

Next.js

Nuxt.js

Node.js

Express.js

Svelte

React Three Fiber

Redux

**Tailwindcss** 

Jest

Cypress

VITE

HTML/CSS/SCSS

And much more ...

## Language

English B2/C1

Russian A2/B1

## **Experience**

O 2022 - 2023

Mizuno

### **Backend Developer**

**Mizuno** is a global corporation which makes a wide variety of sports equipment and sportswear.

#### Responsibilities:

- Developed maintained, and troubleshoot server-side code in SFCC.
- Designed and implemented RESTful APIs.
- Implemented and customized SFCC features such as promotions, checkout flows, etc..
- · Documented code and processes to ensure knowledge transfer and maintainability.
- Participated in code reviews and ensured code quality and best practices.

#### 2023 - 2023

Lookers

## **Frontend Developer**

Soho House is a global hotel chain and group of private members' clubs originally aimed at those in the arts and media.

#### Responsibilities:

- Developed and maintained web application using React.js
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams.
- Participated in code reviews.
- Wrote and maintaining technical documentation.
- Identified and addressing performance issues.

#### 2022 - 2023

**CERN & EPAM** 

### **PEER MENTOR**

I had the privilege of being a mentor at CERN & EPAM, where I guided students through the world of frontend development. My focus was on imparting practical knowledge, including the fundamentals of HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, and Three.js. It was truly rewarding to watch these budding developers grasp the intricacies of web design and interactive graphics, right at the heart of scientific innovation.

#### 2022 - 2023

Freelance

### **Software Developer**

I worked on a variety of projects for clients, using a wide range of programming languages and technologies. My expertise covered web development & Backend. I'm committed to staying updated with new technologies and enjoy turning ideas into functional code.

## **Addition**

#### **Education**

Currently studying Computer Science in Georgian Technical University

### **Participation**

Teaching students Front-End Developement